chillysbottles.com 2018-12-12

# Privacy Policy of www.chillysbottles.com

## Personal Data collected for the following purposes and using the following services:

  *     * ### Analytics

      * ### Google Analytics, Google Ads conversion tracking, Google Tag Manager and Facebook Ads conversion tracking

Personal Data: Cookies and Usage Data

    * ### Contacting the User

      * ### Contact form

Personal Data: email address, first name and last name

    * ### Handling payments

      * ### PayPal and Stripe

Personal Data: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service

    * ### Managing contacts and sending messages

      * ### MailChimp

Personal Data: email address

    * ### Platform services and hosting

      * ### Shopify

Personal Data: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service

    * ### Remarketing and behavioral targeting

      * ### AdWords Remarketing, Remarketing through Google Analytics for Display Advertising and Facebook Remarketing

Personal Data: Cookies and Usage Data

## Further information about Personal Data

  *     * ### Trustpilot

It's in our legitimate business interests to collect reviews from our customers (if they wish to provide such information) so that we can understand feedback on our products and services to improve these over time and so that other customers can also view feedback on our products. We always consider our interests alongside your privacy rights and we make sure your privacy rights are respected. 

    * ### Selling goods and services online

The Personal Data collected are used to provide the User with services or to sell goods, including payment and possible delivery.  
The Personal Data collected to complete the payment may include the credit card, the bank account used for the transfer, or any other means of payment envisaged. The kind of Data collected by this Application depends on the payment system used.

  *     * ### Owner and Data Controller

Chilly's Bottles Ltd

**Owner contact email:** privacy@chillysbottles.com
